(お登勢)あぁ わかってるよ｡
(お岩)大丈夫さ｡
(旦那)根を詰めすぎるなよ｡
そろそろ着く頃だろうよ｡
(お岩)ﾌｯ 相変わらずさ｡
お前が倒れちまったら
この宿は…｡
((お岩:さて 今日も一日
がんばらないとね！
昔から ここは
何にも変わっちゃいないよ｡
そう 昔からね｡
それより
そっちは どうなんだい？
あぁ 忙しいのは お互いさまだよ｡
(旦那)ﾌｯ せいがでるな｡
そりゃそうだよ｡
安心しな
活きのよさだけは保証するって｡
だって 約束しただろ？
ﾎﾝﾄ 何にも変わっちゃいないさ｡
お客さんに喜んでもらうためには
毎日しっかり がんばらないとね｡
あぁ そうだったな｡
Yes, I know.
They should be arriving shortly. Yes, we're all busy.
[A request from me, Otose.]
[Please turn on the lights and keep your distance from the television when watching the show.]
さぁ 行くよ ﾚｲ｡
(ﾚｲ)はい！))
《旦那:約束だ｡
Don't worry. The one thing I can guarantee is that they're a lively bunch.
この宿も お前も ｵﾚが守る》
But how are things on your side?
Oh, the usual. Everything's the same as before on this side.
Really, nothing's changed at all...
since the old days.
All right, let's work hard again today!
Heh, you're awfully energetic.
Well, of course.
We have to do our best every day so that our customers are satisfied.
Well, don't overdo it. If anything should happen to you, this inn will...
It will all be okay.
Because you promised me, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Now let's go, Rei.
Okay!
It's a promise.
I'll protect this inn...and you.
(新八)
ずいぶん山奥まで来ましたね｡
We're pretty deep in the mountains.
(銀時)ﾊﾞｱさんの話じゃ
知る人ぞ知る秘湯って話だからな｡
According to the old lady, it's a hidden hot spring known only to a few.
(お妙)この時期は温泉なんて
どこも予約で いっぱいなのに➡
The hot springs are all booked up during this time of year.
こんな所で
ゆっくり お湯に浸かって➡
It's like a dream to be able to spend our winter break resting and
冬休みが過ごせるなんて
夢みたいね｡
relaxing in the baths at a place like this.
Otose knows the Okami, so she was able to get us rooms.
たしか女将さんが
お登勢さんの古い友人とかで➡
融通きかせてくれたらしいです｡
Go spend some time relaxing in the baths for a change.
((たまには ゆっくり
湯にでも浸かって休んできな))
いやぁ いいところありますよね
お登勢さん｡
I gotta say, Mrs. Otose can be nice sometimes.
ｵﾚは どうにも
胸騒ぎがすんだけど➡
I have a bad feeling about this.
あの ばばあが
こういうﾏﾈするときは➡
When that old hag does something like this, there's usually a catch.
だいたい裏があるんだよ｡
When you can't accept someone's goodwill with an open heart, it's over for you.
人の好意を素直に
受け止められなくなったら➡
人間おしまいですよ｡
(ｶﾗｽの鳴き声)
["Fights Often Ensue During Trips"]
(お妙)あら 道を間違えたかしら｡
廃屋しかないわ｡
I wonder if we took the wrong road.
There's just this dilapidated old building.
(神楽)新八 お前
地図も読めないｱﾙか？
Shinpachi, can't you even read a map?
あれ おかしいな｡ たしか ここで
合ってたはずなんだけど…｡
That's strange. It's supposed to be right here.
え～と 仙望郷ですよね？
Let's see... It's called Senbokyo, right?
あ！ あれ あの看板…➡
Huh? This sign?
[Welcome to the Senbokyo Hot Springs]
仙望郷って書いてませんか？
Doesn't it say Senbokyo?
字がたれて えらく
おどろおどろしくなってますけど｡
The paint seems to have run and it looks all eerie, but...
なんか ここみたいなんですけど｡
I think...this is the place.
これ 温泉 入ってる
おじいさんの絵が…｡
This is a picture of an old man taking a soak.
ﾏｼﾞかい こんなﾎﾞﾛ旅館に泊まんの
ｵﾚたち!?
Are you kidding?! We're supposed to stay in this rundown inn?
っつうか ここ
ﾎﾝﾄに営業してんの？
I mean, is this place really open? I don't see any signs of people.
人の気配がねえぞ！
私たち 人さがしてきます｡
行こう 神楽ちゃん｡
We'll go look for someone. Let's go, Kagura.
おいおい 勘弁してくれよ｡
Hey hey, give me a break! This is definitely a haunted house.
こんなもん完全に
妖怪の住まいじゃねえか！
薄気味悪いよ｡ なんで こんなに
いっぱいｶﾗｽが飛んでんだ？
It's really creepy. Why are there so many crows flying around?
I don't have spiritual powers or anything, but it feels sorta, you know.
なんかﾎﾞｸ 別に霊感とかないけど
ここ なんか あれなんですけど…｡
あれって何だよ？
いや 別に…｡
What do you mean, "you know"?
Never mind.
ちょっと やめてくんない？
頼むから やめてくんない？
Cut it out, will you? I mean really.
あっ いた！
人がいたぞ 従業員か？
Hey, there's someone. An employee?
すみませ～ん ﾎﾞｸら
江戸の寺田さんの紹介で➡
Excuse me! Mrs. Terada from Edo referred us here.
来た者なんですけど
すみませ～ん！
Excuse me!
聞こえねえのかな？
Maybe she can't hear.
なんだよ いてぇな｡
ぎ… 銀さん あ… あの人➡
That hurts!
G-Gin ... That person...
雪の上を歩いているのに➡
She's walking on the snow, yet...
足跡が ついてない｡
there are...no footprints.
ど ど ど… どうなってんだ
あれ！
Wh-Wh-What's going on?!
Was that a ghost? Huh? A ghost?!
ｵ… ｵﾊﾞｹか？ ｵﾊﾞｹなのか!?
No way! Not in broad daylight!
そんなわけあるか お前
白昼堂々 ｵﾊﾞｹって お前！
ないない 絶対な～い
許さん 絶対に許さ～ん！
No way! Absolutely not! No way, I won't allow it! I absolutely won't allow it!
ちょっと 落ちついてください
銀さん｡
Please calm down, Gin!
Pr-Probably when you're this deep in the mountains,
き きっと
こんな山の中ですから➡
昨日 降り積もった雪も凍って➡
there's so much snow that it freezes over and you don't leave footprints.
足跡がつかないくらい
固くなってたんですよ｡
あっ そうだ 絶対そうだ｡
Oh, you're right. That must be it.
ないない 絶対な～い
許さん 絶対に許さん！
No way! No way, absolutely not!
I won't allow it! I absolutely won't allow it!
でも あの人
なんか様子も変でしたね｡
But she acted a bit strange, didn't she?
声が届いてないっていうか
軽く半透明じゃなかったでした？
She didn't hear your voice and...
Didn't she sorta look semi-transparent?
お前さ いい加減にしろよ｡
Hey, cut it out, will you?! I said there's no way!
何もなかったって
言ってんじゃん！
半透明がなんだよ 今時な
ｺﾞﾐ袋だって半透明の時代だよ｡
What's wrong with being semi-transparent?
Even grocery bags these days are semi-transparent!
いるよ 半透明の人くらい｡
So there must be people who are semi-transparent, too!
なに？ お前 ﾋﾞﾋﾞｯてんの？
ひょっとして お前 ﾋﾞﾋﾞｯてる？
What? Are you scared? Don't tell me you're scared?!
いいんだよ
べつに あれだけど帰ろうか？
Well, it's okay. If you insist, we can go home. Wanna go home?
お前が そんなに言うなら
帰ろうか？
いちばん帰りたがってんの
ｱﾝﾀでしょうが｡
You're the one who wants to go home!
だいたい 帰るっつったって➡
Besides, even if we wanted to go home,
ここ１日に ﾊﾞｽ１本しか
来ないくらいですから➡
there's only one bus that passes through this place each day.
今日は泊まるしかないですよ｡
えっ!?
We have no choice but to spend the night.
ちょっと… もう やめねえ？
せっかく温泉に来たのに➡
Let's stop this already.
We're here at a hot springs inn. And look at us.
なに この感じ
考えすぎだよ 気のせいだよ｡
We're over-imagining things. Let's try to brighten up and enjoy this.
せっかくなんだから
もっと こう楽しもうや｡
そうっすよね 気のせいですよね｡
ごめんなさい｡
You're right. It's our imagination.
Sorry, if I said things to scare you, Gin.
銀さん 怖がらせるようなこと
言っちゃって｡
いやいや いやいや
全然 謝ってる意味がわからん｡
I don't know why you're apologizing.
怖いって なに？ ﾎﾜｯﾂ？ 誰か
怖いって感情 ｵﾚに教えてくれ｡
Scared? What's that? Tell me how that feels!
銀ちゃん いたいた 女将｡
あっ よかった｡
Gin! We found the Okami!
Oh, that's good. See, Gin, they're open for business.
ちゃんと 営業してたみたいですよ
銀さん｡
やっぱり 大丈夫ですよ ここ｡
There's nothing wrong with this place.
(お岩)すみません｡
I'm so sorry.
(お岩)もう来てらしたのね｡
You arrived already? Thank you for coming so far.
まぁ 今日は
わざわざ 遠いところから➡
ありがとうございました｡
Welcome. I am the Okami, Oiwa.
どうも 私 当旅館の女将
お岩です｡
《えっ!? どっち？
女将 どっち？》
Huh? Which is the Okami? Huh, which one?
ごめんなさいね
出迎え 遅れてしまって｡
I'm sorry I was late to welcome you.
なにぶん この旅館 おばさん
１人で 切り盛りしてるもんでね｡
I run this place all alone, so...
《いや もう１人いるんですけど｡
明らかに 後ろに もう１人➡
Umm...no, there is someone else.
There's definitely someone behind you.
半透明の従業員が
いるんですけど！》
Someone who's semi-transparent!
《おい！ なんだ あれ？
なんか 背負ってんぞ｡
Hey! What is that?!
She's carrying something on her back! Is it a baby?
赤ちゃんか？ 赤ちゃんだよね
赤ちゃんだと言ってくれ！》
It's a baby, right?! Please say it is!
《そう思いたい でも 半透明です
はっきりと半透明です！》
That's what I'd like to think!
But it's semi-transparent! It's really semi-transparent!
So, what's wrong with being semi-transparent?!
《半透明が なんだよ 今時な
政治家だって半透明の時代だよ｡
In this day and age, even politicians are semi-transparent!
みんな 汚職とか
悪いことやってんだよ｡
They're all involved in shady deals and graft!
いるよ 半透明の赤ん坊くらい》
《いや でも おかしいですよ｡
So there's bound to be a semi-transparent baby!
But it's strange. Sister and Kagura aren't reacting at all!
The place isn't so bad. This is my first time at a Hot Springs.
姉上たちが
まったく ﾘｱｸｼｮﾝなしです｡
あんな不気味な赤ん坊 見たら➡
Anyone would react upon seeing a baby like that!
Oh, really?
普通 何らかのﾘｱｸｼｮﾝを
示しますよ｡
I'm going to get my skin all smooth!
見えてないんですよ
姉上たちには｡
They don't see it. We're the only ones!
あれ見えてるの
ﾎﾞｸらだけなんですよ｡
霊感なんてないと思ってたけど
間違いない 霊だ｡
I didn't believe in spirits...
But that is a ghost! The Okami is totally possessed by a spirit!
女将 思いっきり
霊に とりつかれてる！
いや 女将だけじゃない
さっき見た あれといい…｡
No, it's not only the Okami. What I saw earlier...
この温泉旅館 かなり
やばい所なんじゃないですか!?》
Isn't this hot spring inn like super dangerous?!
Don't be ridiculous!
ﾊﾞ… ﾊﾞｶ 言ってんじゃねえよ｡
幽霊旅館？ ありえねえよ！
A ghost inn?! Impossible.
違う！ 絶対 違う！
認めん！ 絶対 認めん！
No way. Absolutely not.
I will not acknowledge that! I absolutely refuse to believe that!
Then how do you explain that thing on the Okami?
じゃあ 女将のあれ
どう 説明するんですか？
Well... I thought it couldn't be...
いや…
ｵﾚも まさかとは思ったけどな➡
but I think my hunch is right.
どうやら ｵﾚの勘が
当たっちまったらしい｡
あの女将…｡
That Okami...
ｽﾀﾝﾄﾞ使いだ！
[We named it "Stand" from it being Stand by me!]
is a  Stand User.
[No way!]
違うだろ！
How can there be a Stand like that, you idiot?!
あんなｽﾀﾝﾄﾞ あるか ﾎﾞｹ！
どう考えても ｽﾀﾝﾄﾞだろ？ あれ｡
No matter how you look at it, that's a Stand.
I mean, basically, we're Stand Users too.
基本 ｵﾚたちも ｽﾀﾝﾄﾞ使いだろ？
That's why we were able to see the Okami's Stand.
だから 見えたんだよ
女将のｽﾀﾝﾄﾞが｡
ちょ… 待ってください｡ いつから
ｽﾀﾝﾄﾞ使いになったんですか ﾎﾞｸら｡
Hold on! Since when did we become Stand users?!
ｵﾚは ふだん 隠してるけど お前
いつも ｽﾀﾝﾄﾞ 出してるじゃん｡
I usually hide it. But you always show your Stand.
That thing hanging on your ear!
その耳にかかってるﾔﾂ｡
それ ただの眼鏡使いだろ！
That's just a spectacles user!
"That thing hanging on your ear"?!
なんだよ!?
耳にかかってるﾔﾂって！
You know full well what it is. They're spectacles!
言えよ！ 眼鏡って知ってるだろ｡
へぇ～！
眼鏡っていうんだ そのｽﾀﾝﾄﾞ｡
Oh, you call that Stand "Spectacles"?
腹立つ… ｺｲﾂ 腹立つ｡
He's pissing me off. This guy is so pissing me off.
そこまでして 霊の存在
認めたくないんですか｡ 情けない｡
Are you that determined to disavow the existence of a spirit? You're pitiful!
だって 見てくださいよ あれ！
I mean, take a look at that!
あれ？ 霊が消えた…｡
霊じゃない｡ ｽﾀﾝﾄﾞだ！
Huh? The spirit is gone.
It wasn't a spirit. That was a Stand!
あれ… どこ 行ったんだろう？
Huh, where'd it go?
おい… ひょっとして
幻覚だったんじゃねえか？
Hey, maybe it was an illusion?
Are you saying that we were so scared that we saw something that really wasn't there?
あまりにも ﾋﾞﾋﾞってたから➡
見えないものも 見えるように
なってたっていうんですか？
いや そういうことに
しておきましょう｡
Well, let's leave it at that.
あんな存在 認めて ここに
泊まれるほど 度胸ないです｡
I don't have the guts to acknowledge such a presence, and then spend the night here.
You're right. It was just an illusion.
そうだ 幻覚だったんだ｡
あれは ｵﾚたちの心の弱さが
生み出した 悪魔だったんだ｡
It was a demon that our weak minds conjured up.
We'd better shape up. We're samurai. How shameful!
しっかりしねえといけねえな｡
侍が情けない｡
そうですね 温泉だからって
浮かれてちゃ ﾀﾞﾒなんですよ｡
Yes. We can't get lackadaisical just because we've come to a hot springs inn.
Samurai must always be upright and alert!
侍は いつでも
しゃんとしてなきゃ｡
あの… 部屋が 結構 狭くてね
４人で使うのは きついから➡
The rooms are quite small.
It's tough for four people, so I prepared two rooms.
２部屋 用意したんだけど 和式と
洋式 どちらがいいかしらね？
Which do you prefer? Japanese-style or western-style rooms?
洋式なんか あるｱﾙか！
You have western-style rooms?
たまには ﾍﾞｯﾄﾞで寝るのも
いいかしらね｡
Sleeping on a bed would be nice for a change.
Japanese style!
和式で！
侍なんで ﾎﾞｸら！
We're samurai, after all!
はい はい… じゃあ
お侍さんたちは こちらです｡
Yes, fine.
You samurai will be...
...in this room.
(２人)あぁ～！
The room is sealed!
《封じられてる！ 明らかに
巨大な魔を封じた痕跡がある!!
Those are clear signs that some giant beast has been sealed inside!
なんだよ!? これ！ いったい
何があったんだよ？ この部屋で》
What's going on?! Just what happened inside this room?!
《やばいですよ！ やっぱり
この旅館 絶対 おかしいです》
This is bad. There is something definitely strange about this inn!
The young ladies are over this way.
(お岩)お嬢さんたちは こっち｡
す… すみません！
Err, excuse me! Can we change to western-style?
やっぱり ﾎﾞｸら 洋式に
変えてもらっていいですか？
Huh?! But you're samurai.
えっ!? 侍なのに？
Well, actually fake samurai... as in, sham-urai.
侍って いっても ﾎﾞｸら
まがいもんなんで｡ ｻﾑﾗｰｲなんで｡
でも お嬢さん方
もう 行ってしまったから…｡
But the ladies took that room.
えっ!? 何か 気に食わなかった？
Why? Is there something you didn't like?
気に食わなかったっていうか
これ このふすま…｡
Well, rather than didn't like...
The sliding doors...
Oh, you didn't like the design of this door?
あぁ このふすまのﾃﾞｻﾞｲﾝ
気に食わなかった？
ﾃﾞｻﾞｲﾝ!? ﾃﾞｻﾞｲﾝなんですか？ これ！
Design? This is the design?!
(お岩)あの…
一時期なんだけどね➡
Well, there was a time when I was really into rock.
おばさん ﾛｯｸに
ﾊﾏってた時期があってね｡
Rock?! This is punk rock?
ﾛｯｸ!? ﾛｯｸなんですか？ これ！
My name, Oiwa, means rock, you know?
もともと 私のお岩って名前も
ﾛｯｸから来てるからね｡
And these things were all the rage back then. Even I was young at one time.
あの頃は こういうのが
かっこいいと思ってて…｡
まぁ… おばさんも若かったわ｡
ﾛｯｸっつうか これ 別のものを
ﾛｯｸしてるよね？ 違うﾛｯｸだよね？
It's not "rock." It's something different. More like "lock."
[The seals have writing like "forbidden," "taboo," "dangerous," etc.]
(お岩)あっ！ ひょっとして
このお札を気にしてるのかい？
Oh! Could it be these seals are bothering you?
えっ!? あの… はい まぁ…｡
Huh? Umm, yes.
Oh, come on!
(お岩)ちょっと ｲﾔだよ！
ｱﾊﾊﾊ！ そういうこと？
Is that it? Oh no. These are different.
ごめんね｡ 違うのよ｡
これは そういうんじゃないの｡
Well, these are... I hate to admit this to you as the Okami...
いや… これはね 女将の私が
こんなこと 言うのも➡
あれなんだけどね 前にこの部屋に
子連れの人が泊まったのよ｡
But a guest with a child stayed here before.
…で その子供がね
旅行で はしゃいじゃって➡
And the child misbehaved and put holes in the sliding doors.
ふすまに
穴開けちゃったのよ ﾌﾌﾌﾌ…｡
Oh! Is that it? So these are to hide the holes?
ああ！ そういうこと？
えっ？ じゃあ これ
穴を隠すために？
(お岩)ｼｯ！ 内緒よ｡
これ絶対 内緒よ｡
Shh! This is a secret. You must not tell anyone!
な～んだよ｡ それなら そうと
早く言ってくれよな｡
Is that all? You should have just told us sooner.
深読みしちゃったよ 女将さん｡
We imagined the worst, Okami!
(お岩)笑いごとじゃないわよ｡
This is no laughing matter. It was really terrible with holes everywhere.
ﾎﾝﾄ ひどかったんだから
穴だらけで｡
I taught the boy a lesson after that, for one hour.
もう そっから
その子供に小一時間説教｡
Really, I shouldn't have been so harsh on him over a few holes in the sliding door.
ﾎﾝﾄ… ふすまくらいで
あんなに叱るんじゃなかった｡
Full turn left!
(銀時/新八)面舵一杯で急ｶｰﾌﾞ！
Hey! How dare you barge into a lady's room?!
(神楽)おい！ ﾚﾃﾞｨｰの部屋に
急に飛び込んできて➡
何考えてるｱﾙか!?
Wh-What's this commotion all about?
(お妙)な… なに!?
どうしたの そんなに慌てて！
Did something happen?
何か あったの？
銀さん！ 安全確認ｵｯｹｰです！
Gin! All clear! I don't see it anywhere.
どこにも見当たりません！
よし！
Okay!
頼む！ ｵﾚらと部屋代わってくれ！
Please! Change rooms with us!
Huh?
はぁ？
いやぁ やっぱ洋式が➡
I have this sudden urge to stay in a western-style room!
急に使いたくなって…｡
We're not samurai or anything, merely pigs!
ｵﾚら もう侍でも なんでもない
ただのﾌﾞﾀ野郎なんだよ！
Hey? This is western-style? Didn't you ask for a western-style room?
って あれ？ 洋式？
そういや お前ら 洋式の部屋
選んだんじゃなかったのかよ｡
ここ普通に和室じゃねえか｡
This is a Japanese-style room.
ええ そうだったんだけど➡
Yes, we asked for one.
部屋に入ったら
普通に和室だったのよ｡
But when we entered, we found this Japanese-style room.
どこが洋式なんだか…｡
I don't know what's western about it.
Now you know, so leave!
わかったら さっさと出てけよ｡
狭い部屋にﾜｻﾜｻ ｳｻﾞｲｱﾙ！
It's small in here and you're crowding us. There is no western-style room!
(神楽)洋式なんて
どこにもないんだよ！
うわっ!?
《よ… 洋式って！》
W-Western-style room ...
...as in that kind?!
《そこかぁ～!!》
Why?! Why's there a foreigner Stand over there?! I don't understand!
なんで!?
なんで こんなところに➡
外人のｽﾀﾝﾄﾞが いるんだよ！
意味わかんねえよ！
っつうか どうなってるんですか！
この旅館!!
What's with this inn?! This place is full of Stands!
どこもかしこも
ｽﾀﾝﾄﾞだらけじゃないですか!!
さっきから
いったい何を騒いでるんですか？
What are you shouting about? Stand?
ｽﾀﾝﾄﾞ？
いやぁ すみません！
Oh, sorry. It's just something between us.
なんでもないんです｡
こっちの話です｡
世の中にはな 知らねえほうが
いいこともあるんだよ｡
You're better off not knowing about some things in the world.
There seems to be something up.
ただごとじゃ なさそうｱﾙな｡
ごまかさないで
ちゃんと話してください｡
Don't try to hide it. Tell me. We'll hear you out.
私たち ちゃんと聞きますから｡
(お妙)何聞かされても
驚きませんから｡
Nothing you say will shock me.
(２人)あ… あのさ…｡
Oh, well...
(２人)うっ!?
おやつﾀｲﾑ！
Refreshment time!
Here you go. I brought you an afternoon snack.
ほらほら 皆さん
３時のお菓子 持ってきましたよ｡
あっ すみません 女将さん｡
お構いなく｡
Oh, thank you very much! But don't trouble yourself.
(お岩)いえいえ
ゆっくりしていって｡
Oh no, I want you to stay and relax. Think of this as your own home.
ﾎﾝﾄ 自分の家だと思って
いいからね｡
あっ お風呂掃除したから
いつでも入ってね｡
Oh, I prepared the bath, so go and soak anytime.
(お妙)はい！
ありがとうございます｡
Yes, thank you.
しゃべったら殺すぞ｡
If you say anything, I'll kill you.
ﾌﾌﾌﾌ…｡
《おっ… 女将!?》
Th-The Okami!
Wh-What's the meaning of this?!
《な… 何だよ あれ!?
ど… どういうことだ おい！
何者だ あの ばばあ！》
Who is that old hag?!
She knows! That Okami knows all about this!
《気づいてます！ 女将さん完全に
すべてのことに気づいてます！》
《気づくどころか お前
ｽﾀﾝﾄﾞをﾋﾟｰﾅｯﾂで餌付けしてたぞ！
Not only that! She was feeding the Stand those peanuts!
とんでもねえ！
ｵﾚたち とんでもねえところに➡
Man, we've come to a crazy place!
足を踏み入れちまった…｡
この温泉宿は
あの ばばあが飼いならした➡
This hot springs inn...
is swarming with those evil spirits nurtured by that old hag.
悪霊どもが巣食う
死の温泉宿だったんだ～!!》
It's a hot spring inn of death!
No way!
(神楽)銀ちゃん！ 新八！
Gin! Shinpachi!
We're leaving! We must get off this mountain immediately!
脱出だ！
一刻も早く山を下りるんだ！
こんなところに長居してれば
確実に死霊どものえじきだぞ！
If we stick around here, we'll end up as fodder for the ghosts for sure!
ﾊﾞｽなんか かまってられるか！
Never mind waiting for the bus! We'll make a run for it now!
走って 山を下りるぞ！
はい～！
Right!
≪お～い！
そっち側に人はいるかのう？
Hey! Is there anyone on that side?
Looks like there's been a landslide and the road is blocked.
どうも落石で 完全に山道➡
塞がっちまったみてえでな｡
しばらく 山は下りらんねえど｡
You won't be able to come down the mountain for a while.
まぁ そっち側には
温泉宿があるらしいから➡
Well, there should be a hot springs inn over there,
so ask them to put you up there.
しばらく
そこに逗留させてもらいな｡
幽霊が出るなんてｳﾜｻも
あるがのう｡
There are rumors that it's haunted, though.
ﾊｯﾊｯﾊｯ…！
Huh? Why aren't you laughing, too?
あれ 笑い声が聞こえんぞ!?
冗談だってばよ！
I'm just joking!
ﾊｯﾊｯﾊｯﾊ…！
ﾊﾊ… ｱﾊﾊﾊ…｡
(２人)ﾊﾊﾊﾊ…｡
ﾌﾟﾊｰｯ ﾌｩ｡
(お妙)いい お湯ねぇ｡
Isn't it such a nice bath?
この温泉
最初は古くて心配したけど➡
This inn looked so old, I was worried at first.
なかなか いい温泉じゃない｡
この古さも 味に見えてきたわね｡
But it's quite nice. Its age is beginning to appeal to me.
(神楽)何より
客が全然いないのがいいｱﾙ！
I like the fact that there's no other guests.
私たちの貸し切りﾈ！
やりたい放題ｱﾙ！
It's like we have the whole place to ourselves.
We can do whatever we like. I can pee in the water and no one will scold me.
風呂で ｵｼｯｺしても
誰にも文句言われないﾈ！
(お妙)私が 言うわよ｡
I will scold you.
And it seems we're not the only guests.
それに どうやらお客さんは
私たちだけじゃないみたいよ｡
ｳｷｷ… ｷｷｯ！
ﾎｯﾎｯ！
(神楽)うおぉぉ～！
近藤 お前も来てたｱﾙか!?
Kondo, you're here too?!
(お妙)いや 違うわよ 神楽ちゃん｡
No, you're wrong, Kagura.
The monkeys came from the mountain to soak in the baths.
山から おｻﾙさんたちも
お湯に入りに来てたのね｡
Maybe they're females who want nice, smooth skin?
美肌効果を狙った
女の子かしら ｳﾌ！
They're hairy, sneaky ones.
体じゅう毛だるまのくせに
こざかしいﾔﾂらｱﾙ｡
ｹﾂだけ ﾌﾟﾘﾝになって終わりｱﾙ｡
Only their butts are smooth.
まぁ こんな温泉も
たまには いいじゃない｡
Well, it's still a nice hot spring.
銀さん！
そっちの湯加減は どうですか？
Gin, how are you doing on your side?
Huh? I wonder if something happened?
(お妙)あら どうかしたのかしら｡
(神楽)銀ちゃん！ 新八！
のぼせたｱﾙか？
Gin! Shinpachi! Did you guys get dizzy from a long bath?!
なんか… いっぱい… 来てる…｡
There...are so...many.
(お妙)あら まぁ！
そっちにも おｻﾙさんが？
Oh, you mean there are monkeys on your side too?
いや… なんか変なのが…！
No. They're really strange.
(神楽)どうしたｱﾙか？
What's the matter?! Are you surrounded by guys with tattoos?!
入れ墨もんにでも囲まれたｱﾙか？
ﾋｬﾊﾊﾊﾊ…！
Kagura! What if you're right?
(お妙)神楽ちゃん
ﾎﾝﾄにいたら どうするの？
Sorry, all you tattooed people!
(神楽)ごめんなさ～い！
入れ墨もんの皆さん｡
他意は ないんです｡
あの お気を悪くされたのなら➡
I didn't mean to insult you.
But if you're upset, please feel free to throw those two into a pool of cement.
どうぞ その男たち
ｺﾝｸﾘ風呂なりなんなり➡
ﾌﾞﾁ込んでやってください！
ﾋｬﾊﾊﾊﾊﾊ…！
入れ墨もんなら
どれだけよかったことか…｡
Tattooed people would have been so much better.
I'd be so happy, I'd jump into the cement or into the deep sea voluntarily!
もう いっそ喜んで
ｺﾝｸﾘ風呂にも海の底にも➡
飛び込みますよ ﾎﾞｸは｡
気絶しろぉぉ！
Faint! Knock myself out!
ｵﾚ 気絶しろぉぉ！
銀さぁ～ん！
Gin!
Damn it! Why won't I faint?! Stupid!
ｸｿｯ なんで気絶しねえんだ！
ｵﾚのﾊﾞｶ 死ね ｵﾚ！
落ち着いてください 銀さん！
Die!
Calm down, Gin!
Get a hold of yourself!
気を しっかり持ってください！
ｲﾔだ 絶対しっかり持たねえ！
No way! I so won't get a hold of myself!
ﾌﾞﾗ～ﾝってぶらさげる！
ﾙｰｽﾞに 今風に 腰ではく！
I'll hang it loosely upside down!
I'll wear my pants hanging at the hip.
What's with this hot spring?! What's with those things in the bath?!
何なんだよ この温泉！
何で あんなんが
湯つかってんだよ!?
水場には 霊が集まりやすいとは
聞いてたけど こんなっ…！
I've heard that spirits gather where there's water, but this is...
They're not spirits, they're Stands!
霊じゃねえ ｽﾀﾝﾄﾞだ！
霊とか言うな！
Don't call them spirits!
あれ？ ちょっと待て｡
Huh? Hey, wait a minute.
よく見たら
ｺｲﾂら湯気じゃね これ？
On closer inspection, could it be the steam?
いや 違います｡
いや 湯気だよ これ｡
No, you're wrong.
No, it's the steam.
ﾋﾞﾋﾞりまくって人の形に
見えてるだけじゃん 半透明だし｡
It's just swirling around and looks like people, semi-transparent people.
新八 ちょっと ｺｲﾂら
吸い込んでみ｡ うってなるから｡
Shinpachi, breathe it in. You'll get morning sickness.
Why're we talking about a pregnant woman now?!
なんで妊婦みたいになってんだよ｡
I said...
いいから吸ってみ って
言ってんだよ！
...breathe!
ｷﾞｬ～ｯ！
ｺﾞﾎｯ ｺﾞﾎｯ… 何すんですか！
What're you doing?!
ほらほら なんともないじゃん！
See? There's nothing. It was the steam.
やっぱり湯気だ｡
やった 湯気だよ おい！
It was the steam!
う～ん… ﾎﾝﾄだ｡
Oh, you're right.
何でもないっすね！
[Cursed]
It was nothing.
とりあえず謝っとくわ すまん｡
Let me just apologize. Sorry.
えっ なんで？
なんかなってんすか？
Huh? Why? Is something wrong?
いや 別に｡
10万16歳みたいになってるだけ｡
Oh, nothing. You just look like you're 100,016 years old.
あっ 銀さん
見えなくなりましたよ！
Hey Gin, they're all gone. I guess it was the steam, after all.
やっぱ湯気だったみたいですよ！
いや 湯気じゃなかった｡
断言できる｡
No, it wasn't the steam. I can verify that.
今のうちにあがりましょう｡
I think we should get out, though.
すっかり
のぼせちゃいましたよ 我が輩｡
The heat is getting to me...myself.
我が輩？ 我が輩って言った 今？
Did you just say you yourself?
なんか我が輩 体が重いな｡
I myself feel a bit heavy.
あっちも
10万16歳みたいになってる！
Even that looks 100,016 years old!
あっちも我が輩になってる！
That itself is changed!
どうしよう お妙に殺される！
え～ 何言ってんすか？
What'll I do?! Otae will kill me!
Huh? What're you saying?
とりあえず もう１回 謝っとくわ｡
ごめんなさい 新八君！
I'd better apologize once more.
I'm sorry, Shinpachi!
(お妙)あ～ いいお湯だった！
あっ 姉上 神楽ちゃん！
Oh, that was a nice soak.
Oh! Sister, Kagura!
(神楽)どうだ 我が輩の肌
ｽﾍﾞｽﾍﾞになったであろう ﾌﾊﾊﾊﾊ！
Look! Our skin is silky smooth!
[Cursed]
誰だぁ!? 誰だ お前ら!?
Who the hell are you?!
Who the hell are you?! Which one's which, and who's who?!
誰が どいつで どいつが誰だ！
何を言っている 我が輩だ｡
What are you saying? It's me!
我が輩だ｡
我が輩だ！
And I myself.
And I myself!
全員 我が輩だろうが！
You're all like that!
どうだ 我が輩の部屋で
UNOでもせんか？
Why don't we go to our room and play UNO?
それはいいな！
よし やろう ﾌﾊﾊﾊ！
That sounds good. Let's play!
我が輩に勝てるかな ﾌﾊﾊﾊ！
I wonder if you can beat me!
《なんてこった…
全員 とりつかれちまった！》
What's going on?! They're all possessed!
って あれ？
ちょっと待ってくれ！
Hey! Wait! Don't leave me here alone! Hey!
ｵﾚを１人にしないでくれ！ おい！
(お岩)ﾌﾌﾌﾌ…！
Okami!
女将… この ばばあ！
Why you...old hag!
ｸｿｯ どこ行きやがった！
出てきやがれ！
Damn it!
Where the hell did you go?!
Come on out!
ﾃﾒｴ いったい ｵﾚたちを
どうするつもりだ！
Damn you! Just what do you intend to do with us?!
何なんだよ この旅館は！
ﾔﾂらを元に戻しやがれ！
Just what is this inn anyway?!
Turn them back to normal!
(幽霊)ﾌﾌﾌﾌ…！
(幽霊)ｺｲﾂは使えるねぇ｡
We can use him.
ああ… ｺｲﾂなら大丈夫だよ｡
Yes, he'll do fine.
うわ～っ！
(拍手)
えっ… えっ？
(お岩)は～い おめでとう！
All right, congratulations!
面接合格！
You've passed the job interview.
えっ…？
[To be continued]
The next episode: "Briefs Will Unavoidably Get Skidmarks"
[For filming the lady's bath scene in today's episode, we got permission from the Okami to have the ladies bathe wearing towels.]
[For you viewers, please abide by the rules when bathing.]